<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://tegant.com/en/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://tegant.com/en/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2019-05-26T08:48:33+01:00</updated><id>https://tegant.com/en/feed.xml</id><entry><title type="html">Our Journey Begins…</title><link href="https://tegant.com/en/blog/2019/05/25/our-journey-begins.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Our Journey Begins..." /><published>2019-05-25T00:00:00+01:00</published><updated>2019-05-25T00:00:00+01:00</updated><id>https://tegant.com/en/blog/2019/05/25/our-journey-begins</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://tegant.com/en/blog/2019/05/25/our-journey-begins.html">&lt;p&gt;Tegant went live a year ago on 17th May 2018.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have come a long way since and have made many improvements. We have overhauled the design and provided global servers for premium subscribers. Video advertisement for free users is now seamless and pain-free.  All these have increased trust in our VPN, and our user base is increasing every day.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are still a small startup company that is growing steadily in a competitive market. We make sure to pass on the price savings to our customers. We provide quality servers for half the price of what NordVPN would charge you.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Follow us on this journey, and we promise to share many exciting stories along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/post-img/german-engineering.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;German Engineering&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;what-can-tegant-do-for-you&quot;&gt;What can Tegant do for you?&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tegant is a powerful VPN app designed to safeguard your online privacy.
In light of what is happening these days with online privacy, you have to be more than ever vigilant about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tegant is very simple to use and is German-engineered.
Tegant protects your WIFI against hackers and fraudsters.
Tegant gives you access to blocked websites and services on your iPhone/iPad – risk-free.
Tegant bypasses censorship when travelling.
Tegant bypasses geo-restrictions of Youtube, Netflix and more.
Tegant is fast.
Tegant uses cutting-edge IKEv2 technology to protect your online privacy from prying eyes.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Tegant went live a year ago on 17th May 2018. We have come a long way since and have made many improvements. We have overhauled the design and provided global servers for premium subscribers. Video advertisement for free users is now seamless and pain-free. All these have increased trust in our VPN, and our user base is increasing every day.</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://tegant.com/en/german-engineering-small.jpeg" /></entry></feed>